Alexander Los you position yourself
александр лось вы позиционируете себя
as a Russian blogger who communicates with
как российский блогер который общается с
Ukrainians in chat-roulette brings them the
украинцами в чат-рулетке доносит к ним
truth shows how they are mistaken you
правду показывает как они заблуждаются
show that you tell your
показываете что рассказываете своим
viewers of Russia, who are hundreds of thousands inspecting there,
зрителям россии которых в осмотра там
that Ukraine started a war in the
сотни тысяч что украина начала войну на
Donbass Ukraine kills its
донбассе украина убивает своих
compatriots complies with the Minsk
соотечественниц соблюдает минские
agreements and
соглашения и
a bunch of such and such things where you
кучу-кучу такого и таких вещей где вы
justify justify Russian
оправдаете оправдываете российскую
aggression against Ukraine I am a Ukrainian
агрессию против украины я украинский
blogger Andriy Popok I challenge you to a
блогер андрей попок я вызываю вас на
blogging duel so we can
блогерскую дуэль так мы можем
meet there on Skype in zoom as it
встретиться там в скайпе в зуме как нам
will be convenient for us in order not
будет удобно для того чтобы там не
to look for each other in the chat for half a year  - roulette,
искать полгода друг друга в чат-рулетке
do not wait for someone to break off the connection
не ждать что там оборвется связь у кого
there, but we can live so
то так а мы сможем в прямом эфире так
your audience will watch you,
вас будут смотреть ваши ваша аудитория
mine and we, in fact, without insults,
меня моя и мы по фактам без оскорблений
without any ridicule,
без каких-то насмешек
will try to figure out who is wrong
попробуем разобраться кто же не прав
Ukraine or Russia
украина или россия
three folders or  Alexander Losev because
три папок или александр лосев потому что
there are only four options here, or I was
тут есть только четыре варианта либо я
somehow mistaken
чем-то заблуждались
second, either I deliberately deceive
второй либо я специально обманывают
people
людей
3 or you are mistaken about something and 4 or
3 либо вы чем-то заблуждаетесь и 4 либо
you deliberately deceive people I think
вы специально обманываете людей я считаю
that this is the fourth option you deliberately
что это четвертый вариант вы специально
deceive people people to whom you
обманываете людей людей которым вы
tell that Ukraine is to blame and
рассказывайте что виновата украина и
influence them so that they
влияете на них для того чтобы они
support this so-called
поддерживали эту так называемую
I’m a Ukrainian blogger Andrey Papak, I
я украинский блогер андрей папок бросаю
’m challenging you to a blogger’s operation Yes, if you’re not
вам вызов на блогерскую да если вы не
afraid if you are ready to answer for your
боюсь если вы готовы отвечать за свои
words, so I want to take the stairs with you and
слова так я хочу лестница с вами и с
discuss all the facts on the air with the
прямом эфире обсудить все факта по
documents,
документам
you already position yourself as a person
уж позиционируете себя как человек
who operates the invoice, I’m waiting  your
который оперирует фактуру я жду вашего
answer if it weren't for Boeing us
ответа если бы не боинг us